ID: AC.L1-3.1.1	Title: Authorized Access Control
Description: Limit information system access to authorized users, processes acting on behalf of authorized users, or devices (including other information systems).

ID: AC.L1-3.1.2	Title: Transaction & Function Control
Description: Limit information system access to the types of transactions and functions that authorized users are permitted to execute. 

ID: AC.L1-3.1.20	Title: External Connections
Description: Verify and control/limit connections to and use of external information systems. 

ID: AC.L1-3.1.22	Title: Control Public Information
Description: Control information posted or processed on publicly accessible information systems.

ID: IA.L1-3.5.1	Title: Identification
Description: Identify information system users, processes acting on behalf of users, or devices.

ID: IA.L1-3.5.2	Title: Authentication
Description: Authenticate (or verify) the identities of those users, processes, or devices, as a prerequisite to allowing access to organizational information systems.

ID: MP.L1-3.8.3	Title: Media Disposal
Description: Sanitize or destroy information system media containing Federal Contract Information before disposal or release for reuse.

ID: PE.L1-3.10.1	Title: Limit Physical Access
Description: Limit physical access to organizational information systems, equipment, and the respective operating environments to authorized individuals. 

ID: PE.L1-3.10.3	Title: Escort Visitors
Description: Escort visitors and monitor visitor activity. 

ID: PE.L1-3.10.4	Title: Physical Access Logs
Description: Maintain audit logs of physical access.

ID: PE.L1-3.10.5	Title: Manage Physical Access
Description: Control and manage physical access devices.

ID: SC.L1-3.13.1	Title: Boundary Protection
Description: Monitor, control, and protect organizational communications (i.e., information transmitted or received by organizational information systems) at the external boundaries and key internal boundaries of the information systems.

ID: SC.L1-3.13.5	Title: Public-Access System Separation
Description: Implement subnetworks for publicly accessible system components that are physically or logically separated from internal networks.

ID: SI.L1-3.14.1	Title: Flaw Remediation
Description: Identify, report, and correct information and information system flaws in a timely manner.

ID: SI.L1-3.14.2	Title: Malicious Code Protection
Description: Provide protection from malicious code at appropriate locations within organizational information systems.

ID: SI.L1-3.14.4	Title: Update Malicious Code Protection
Description: Update malicious code protection mechanisms when new releases are available.

ID: SI.L1-3.14.5	Title: System & File Scanning
Description: Perform periodic scans of the information system and real-time scans of files from external sources as files are downloaded, opened, or executed.

